// let questions = [
//     {
//         numb: 1,
//         question: " I am an boy.",
//         answer: "A. I am a boy",
//         options: [
//             "A. I am a boy",
//             "B. I am boy",
//             "C. I am an boy",
//             "D. I am boying"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 2,
//         question: "They is flowers",
//         answer: "B. They are flowers",
//         options: [
//             "A. They is flower",
//             "B. They are flowers",
//             "C. They are flower",
//             "D. They is flowers"
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 3,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 4,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 5,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 6,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 7,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 8,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 9,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 10,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 11,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 12,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 13,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 14,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 15,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 16,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },

//     {
//         numb: 17,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 18,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 19,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 20,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 21,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 22,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 23,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 24,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         numb: 25,
//         question: "",
//         answer: " ",
//         options: [
//             "A.  ",
//             "B. ",
//             "C. ",
//             "D. "
//         ]
//     }
// ];

// // {
// //         numb: 5,
// //         question: "What does XML stand for?",
// //         answer: "D. Extensible Markup Language",
// //         options: [
// //             "A. Excellent Multiple Language",
// //             "B. Explore Multiple Language",
// //             "C. Extra Markup Language",
// //             "D. Extensible Markup Language"
// //         ]
// //     },











let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: " I am an boy.",
        answer: "A. I am a boy",
        options: [
            "A. I am a boy",
            "B. I am boy",
            "C. I am an boy",
            "D. I am boying"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: " They is flowers.",
        answer: "B. They are flowers",
        options: [
            "A. They is flower",
            "B. They are flowers",
            "C. They are flower",
            "D. They is flowers"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: " They are bus driver.",
        answer: "A. They are bus drivers",
        options: [
            "A. They are bus drivers",
            "B. They are driver",
            "C. They is bus driver",
            "D. They is bus drivers"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: " We is policemen.",
        answer: "B. We are policemen",
        options: [
            "A. We are policeman",
            "B. We are policemen",
            "C. We is policeman",
            "D. We is policemen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: " He is a postwoman.",
        answer: "A. He is a postman",
        options: [
            "A. He is a postman",
            "B. He are a postwoman",
            "C. He is postwoman",
            "D. He is postmans"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: " Julie am twelve.",
        answer: "B. Julie is twelve",
        options: [
            "A. Julie are twelve",
            "B. Julie is twelve",
            "C. Julie am twelve",
            "D. Julie be twelve"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: " They are potatos.",
        answer: "A. They are potatoes",
        options: [
            "A. They are potatoes",
            "B. They is potato",
            "C. They are potato",
            "D. They is potatos"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: " They are babys.",
        answer: "B. They are babies",
        options: [
            "A. They are baby",
            "B. They are babies",
            "C. They is babies",
            "D. They are babys"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: " John and Mary is teachers.",
        answer: "B. John and Mary are teachers",
        options: [
            "A. John and Mary are teacher",
            "B. John and Mary are teachers",
            "C. John and Mary is teacher",
            "D. John and Mary is teachers"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " The cat sleep on the table.",
        answer: "A. The cat sleeps on the table",
        options: [
            "A. The cat sleeps on the table",
            "B. The cat sleeping on the table",
            "C. The cat sleep on table",
            "D. The cats sleep on the table"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: " What is the plural of 'baby'?",
        answer: "C. Babies",
        options: [
            "A. Babys",
            "B. Babyes",
            "C. Babies",
            "D. Babes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " What is the plural of 'mouse'?",
        answer: "A. Mice",
        options: [
            "A. Mice",
            "B. Mouses",
            "C. Mices",
            "D. Mouse"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: " What is the plural of 'tooth'?",
        answer: "B. Teeth",
        options: [
            "A. Tooths",
            "B. Teeth",
            "C. Teeths",
            "D. Toothes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: " What is the plural of 'goose'?",
        answer: "D. Geese",
        options: [
            "A. Gooses",
            "B. Goose",
            "C. Geeses",
            "D. Geese"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: " What is the plural of 'person'?",
        answer: "C. People",
        options: [
            "A. Persons",
            "B. Persones",
            "C. People",
            "D. Peoples"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: " Choose the correct spelling for the number 13:",
        answer: "C. Thirteen",
        options: [
            "A. Thirtean",
            "B. Thirtheen",
            "C. Thirteen",
            "D. Thertin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: " Choose the correct spelling for the number 40:",
        answer: "B. Forty",
        options: [
            "A. Fourty",
            "B. Forty",
            "C. Fortee",
            "D. Forte"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: " Choose the correct spelling for the number 8:",
        answer: "A. Eight",
        options: [
            "A. Eight",
            "B. Aight",
            "C. Eit",
            "D. Eighht"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: " Choose the correct spelling for the number 100:",
        answer: "B. One Hundred",
        options: [
            "A. One Hundrid",
            "B. One Hundred",
            "C. On Hundred",
            "D. One Hundread"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: " Choose the correct spelling for the number 7:",
        answer: "B. Seven",
        options: [
            "A. Seaven",
            "B. Seven",
            "C. Saven",
            "D. Sevven"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: " I ___ a teacher and you ___ a student.",
        answer: "C. am, are",
        options: [
            "A. is, are",
            "B. are, is",
            "C. am, are",
            "D. am, is"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: " He ___ a baker and she ___ a chef.",
        answer: "B. is, is",
        options: [
            "A. are, are",
            "B. is, is",
            "C. am, is",
            "D. are, is"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: " We ___ singers, and they ___ musicians.",
        answer: "A. are, are",
        options: [
            "A. are, are",
            "B. is, is",
            "C. am, is",
            "D. are, is"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: " She ___ a nurse, and he ___ a doctor.",
        answer: "C. is, is",
        options: [
            "A. am, is",
            "B. are, is",
            "C. is, is",
            "D. is, are"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: " You ___ a pilot, and I ___ a flight attendant.",
        answer: "D. are, am",
        options: [
            "A. is, am",
            "B. are, is",
            "C. am, is",
            "D. are, am"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 26,
        question: " What is the number 23 in words?",
        answer: "B. Twenty-three",
        options: [
            "A. One",
            "B. Twenty-three",
            "C. Thirty-three",
            "D. Three"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 27,
        question: " What is the number 5890 in words?",
        answer: "B. Five thousand eight hundred ninety",
        options: [
            "A. Fifty-eight",
            "B. Five thousand eight hundred ninety",
            "C. Five thousand eighty",
            "D. Five hundred eighty"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 28,
        question: " What is the number 256732 in words?",
        answer: "A. Two hundred fifty-six thousand seven hundred thirty-two",
        options: [
            "A. Two hundred fifty-six thousand seven hundred thirty-two",
            "B. Two hundred fifty-six million seven hundred thirty-two",
            "C. Two thousand five hundred sixty-seven hundred thirty-two",
            "D. Two hundred five thousand six hundred thirty-two"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 29,
        question: " What is the number 112478392 in words?",
        answer: "A. One hundred twelve million four hundred seventy-eight thousand three hundred ninety-two",
        options: [
            "A. One hundred twelve million four hundred seventy-eight thousand three hundred ninety-two",
            "B. One hundred twelve million four hundred seventy-eight thousand three hundred twenty-two",
            "C. One hundred twelve million four thousand seven hundred thirty-two",
            "D. One hundred twelve thousand four hundred seventy-eight thousand three hundred ninety-two"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 30,
        question: " What is the number 179299292 in words?",
        answer: "A. One hundred seventy-nine million two hundred ninety-nine thousand two hundred ninety-two",
        options: [
            "A. One hundred seventy-nine million two hundred ninety-nine thousand two hundred ninety-two",
            "B. One hundred seventy-nine million two thousand two hundred ninety-two",
            "C. One hundred seventy-nine billion two hundred ninety-nine thousand two hundred ninety-two",
            "D. One hundred seventy-nine million two hundred thousand two hundred ninety-two"
        ]
    }
];




